Finding aid for the Gene Roddenberry Star Trek Television Series Collection PASC.0062
UCLA Library Special Collections
- PRODUCED EPISODES
  - MIRI (Prod# 12)
    - Financial Materials: Photo Effects (1), Daily budget reports (6), Production reports (3). Total Items: 10 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - MIRROR, MIRROR (Prod# 39)
    - 1) Story outline by Jerome Bixby, 2/27/67, w/annotations, 19 pgs. (2 copies) 2) Story outline, 3/2/67, w/annotations, 17 pgs. 3) Story outline, 4/1/67, 15 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Bixby, Jerome (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Script Materials: DeForest Research (3). Total Items: 3 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Production Materials: Cast List (2), Day-Out-Of-Days (2), Photographic Effects (3). Total Items: 7 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 2/28/67 - 7/20/67. Total Items: 44 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Bay, Don R. * Messerschmidt, Jean * Robertson, Stanley * Roddenberry, Gene * Fontana, D.C. * Justman, Robert (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Financial Materials: Contract Request Form (1), Daily Budget Report (1), Budget & Cost Report (4), Daily Cost Status Reports (6). Total Items: 12 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - MUDD'S WOMEN (Prod# 4)
    - Rough draft "work copy", Pilot Outline, 7/20/64, 24 p. with annotations. Revised outline, 7/23/64, 12 pages, (2 copies) by Gene Roddenberry. Teleplay by Stephen Kandel, n.d., 65 p. (incomplete). Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Kandel, Stephen (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Script materials: Wild Lines, 6 pages, and 7 pages. Kirk's Narration2 pages. Revised pages of scripts, w/annotations. Research comments/DeForest Research, 6/01/66, 3 pages. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Production materials: Shooting Schedule (12), Cast List (4), Casting Appts. (1), Wild Lines (3), Call Sheets (6), Daily Production Reports (8), Credits (3), Revised Credits (3, 3 copies), Revised Credits (3, 4 copies). Total Items: 58 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and memos: incl. letters re script by Harvey P. Lynn.NBC Broadcast Standards Department. Desilu Productions. 28 items. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Financial materials: Production Budget Reports (2), Daily Budget Reports (6). Total Items: 8 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - THE NAKED TIME (Prod# 7)
    - "Preliminary draft", 6/14/66, 68 pages. Another copy, 6/20/66 with annotations. 69 pages. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Script materials: Treatment, n.d. by John D.F. Black, 20 pages with pencil annotations. - Undated story outline by John D.F. Black, 2 copies. Revised pages, dated 7/1/, 7/05, and 8/11/66. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Black, John D.F. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Production Materials: Credits (3), Cast list (2), Daily Production Reports (9). Total Items: 14. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Financial Materials: Production Budget Reports (2). Total Items: 2 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - OBSESSION (Prod# 47)
    - 1) Story Outline by Art Wallace, 5/19/67, 15 pgs. 2) Story Outline, 5/23/67, 15 pgs. 3) Teleplay, 8/10/67, 69 pgs. 4) Teleplay, 7/17/67, 72 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Wallace, Art (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Script Materials: Notes on Story outline by Roddenberry (2), DeForest Research (5). Total Items: 7 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 4/25/66 - 9/7/67. Total Items: 73 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Justman, Robert * Black, John D.F. * Fontana, D.C. * Roddenberry, Gene * Robertson, Stanley * Coon, Gene * Messerschmidt, Jean (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - THE OMEGA GLORY (Prod# 54)
    - 1) Story Outline, 4/20/65, 10 pgs. (2 copies) 2) Story Outline, 4/23/65, 14 pgs. (2 copies, 1 w/annotations) 3) Story outline by Gene Roddenberry, 4/25/65, 21 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Roddenberry, Gene (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - 1) Rough draft teleplay, 4/28/65, 34 pgs. (Incomplete) 2) First draft teleplay by Gene Roddenberry, 5/21/65, w/annotations, 71 pgs. 3) Teleplay, n.d., 32 pgs. (Incomplete) 4) Teleplay, 12/15/67, 40 pgs. (Incomplete) (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 10/4/67 - 2/26/68. Total Items: 10 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Fontana, D.C. * Robertson, Stanley * Messerschmidt, Jean * Roddenberry, Gene * Lucas, John Meredyth * Stahnke, Shirley * Justman, Robert (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - OPERATION .. ANNIHILATE! (Prod# 29)
    - 1) Story outline by Steven W. Carabatsos, 12/15/66, 18 pgs. (2 copies, 1 w/annotations) Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Carabatsos, Steven (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Script Materials: DeForest Research (8). Total Items: 8 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Production Materials: Credits Breakdown (3, 2 copies) Total Items: 6 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, 1/23/67. Total Items: 2 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Robertson, Stanley (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Financial Materials: Production Budget Reports (4). Total Items: 4 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - THE PARADISE SYNDROME (Prod# 58)
    - 1) Story Outline by Maragaret Armen, 3/15/68, w/annotations, 8 pgs. 2) Story Outline, 3/22/68, 12 pgs. 3) First Draft Teleplay, 5/7/68, 76 pgs. 4) Second draft teleplay, 5/18/68, w/annotations, 87 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Armen, Margaret (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Script Materials: Revisions, loose pages (12), DeForest Research (5). Total Items: 17 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 3/15/68 - 6/27/68. Total Items: 63 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Justman, Robert * Robertson, Stanley * Roddenberry, Gene (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Production Materials: Credits Breakdown (3), Shooting Schedule (7), Photographic Effects (3), Call Sheets (6), Daily Production Reports (6). Total Items: 25 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Financial Materials: Budget Report (1), Budget Worksheets (24), Weekly Production Summary (22), Estimated Finished Cost (29). Total Items: 76 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - PATTERNS OF FORCE (Prod# 52)
    - 1) Story Outline by Paul Schneider, 12/13/66, 21 pgs. (2 copies) 2) Story Outline by Paul Schneider, n.d., 19 pgs. 3) Teleplay by Paul Schneider, 6/1/67, 63 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Schneider, Paul * Lucas, John Meredyth (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - 1) Story outline by John Meredyth Lucas, 6/5/67, 27 pgs. 2) Story Outline, 6/24/67, 29 pgs. (2 Copies) 3) Story Outline, 7/7/67, 16 pgs. 4) Story Outline, 7/19/67, 23 pgs. 5) Story Outline, 7/26/67, 18 pgs. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Script Materials: DeForest Research (8). Total Items: 8 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 12/15/66 - 11/12/67. Total Items: 72 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Fontana, D.C. * Roddenberry, Gene * Messerschmidt, Jean * Robertson, Stanley * Justman, Robert * Bay, Don R. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - A PIECE OF THE ACTION (A.K.A. MISSION INTO CHAOS) (Prod# 49)
    - 1) Story Outline by David Harmon, 8/8/67, 18 pgs. 2) Teleplay by David Harmon, 8/16/67, 60 pgs. 3) Second draft teleplay by David Harmon, 9/5/67, 70 pgs. 4) Final draft teleplay by David Harmon & Gene Coon, 10/30/67, 63 pgs. (Incomplete) Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Harmon, David * Coon, Gene (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Script Materials: Revisions, loose pages (15), DeForest Research (6). Total Items: 21 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 8/9/67 - 11/2/67. Total Items: 58 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Justman, Robert * Fontana, D.C. * Coon, Gene * Messerschmidt, Jean (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - PLATO'S STEPCHILDREN (Prod# 67)
    - 1) Story Outline by Meyer Dolinsky, 6/10/68, w/annotations, 21 pgs. 2) First draft teleplay, 7/8/68, 67 pgs. 3) Third draft teleplay, 8/8/68, 63 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Dolinsky, Meyer (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Script Materials: DeForest Research (11). Total Items: 11 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, 6/25/68 - 10/8/68. Total Items: 11 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Robertson, Stanley * Messerschmidt, Jean * Roddenberry, Gene (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Production Materials: Credits Breakdown (3), Photographic EFfects (1), Shooting Schedule (4), Daily Production Reports (8), Call Sheets (7). Total Items: 23 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Financial Materials: Budget Report (1), Budget Worksheets (24), Weekly Production Summary (14), Estimated Finish Cost (17). Total Items: 56 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - A PRIVATE LITTLE WAR (Prod# 45)
    - 1) Story Outline by Don Ingalls, 4/30/67, w/annotations, 12 pgs. 2) Story Outline, 6/1/67, w/annot., 15 pgs. 3) Story Outline, 6/10/67, 15 pgs. 4) 1st draft teleplay, 8/7/67, w/annot., 64 pgs. 5) Teleplay, 9/24/67, w/annot., 51 pgs. (Incomplete) Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Ingalls, Don (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, De Forest Research (4), 5/8/67 - 11/2/67. Total Items: 49 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Roddenberry, Gene * Justman, Robert * Fontana, D.C. * Coon, Gene (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Financial Materials: Budget and Cost Report (29). Total Items: 29 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - REQUIEM FOR METHUSELAH (Prod# 76)
    - 1) Revised Story Outline by Jerome Bixby, 9/2/68, 24 pgs. 2) Story Outline, 9/6/68, 15 pgs. 3) First draft teleplay, 11/4/68, 69 pgs. 4) Teleplay, 11/18/68, 73 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Bixby, Jerome (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Script Materials: DeForest Research (7). Total Items: 7 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, 10/9/68 - 12/9/68. Total Items: 6 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Bays, Donald W. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Production Materials: Shooting Schedule (6), Daily Production Reports (8), Call Sheets (7). Total Items: 21 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Financial Materials: Budget Report (1), Budget Worksheets (24), Weekly Production Summary (6), Estimated Finished Cost (6). Total Items: 37 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - THE RETURN OF THE ARCHONS (Prod# 22)
    - 1) Story Outline by Gene Roddenberry, 7/22/64, 11 pgs. 2) Story Outline by Gene Roddenberry, 7/20/64, 21 pgs. (2 copies, 1 w/annotations). Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Roddenberry, Gene * Sobelman, Boris (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 1) Story outline by Boris Sobelman, 8/28/66 (?), 20 pgs (2 copies) 2) Outline, 8/29/66, 17 pgs. (3 copies) 3) Outline, 8/29/66, 18 pgs. (2 copies) 4) Outline, 9/14/66, 9 pgs. (2 copies) 5) Teleplay (Incomplete), n.d., w/annotations, 44 pgs. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Production Materials: Cast List (7), Daily Production Reports (2). Total Items: 9 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 8/23/66 - 12/9/66. Total Items: 34 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Roddenberry, Gene * Justman, Robert * Coon, Gene * Robertson, Stanley (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - 1) Story Outline by John Dugan, 5/9/67, 21 pgs. 2) Second draft teleplay, 10/11/67, 68 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Dugan, John (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Script Materials: Revisions, loose pages (55). Total Items: 55 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, Writers Guild of America, 5/8/67 - 12/13/67. Total Items: 62 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Dorfman, Mary * Justman, Robert * Fontana, D.C. * Dugan, John * Coon, Gene * Robertson, Stanley * Roddenberry, Gene (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Script Materials: Revisions, loose pages (42), Notes on first draft (3, 2 copies), DeForest Research (5). Total Items: 53 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Financial Materials: Production Budget Report (3), Daily Budget Reports (4). Total Items: 7 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - THE SAVAGE CURTAIN (Prod# 77)
    - 1) Story Outline by Gene Roddenberry, 5/8/68, 30 pgs. 2) Story Outline by Gene Roddenberry, 5/9/68, 26 pgs. 3) Story Outline by Gene Roddenberry, n.d., 35 pgs. (2 copies, 1 w/annotations) Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Roddenberry, Gene * Heinemann, Arthur (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - 1) Teleplay by Gene Roddenberry, 9/11/68, 35 pgs. (Incomplete, 2 copies) 2) Teleplay by Gene Roddenberry and Arthur Heinemann, 11/27/68, 59 pgs. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Script Materials: Revisions, Loose Pages (21), DeForest Research (5). Total Items: 26 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, 5/12/68 - 12/18/68. Total Items: 17 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Roddenberry, Gene (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Production Materials: Shooting Schedule (8), Photographic Effects (3), Call Sheets (6), Daily Production Reports (7). Total Items: 24 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Financial Materials: Budget Report (1), Budget Worksheets (24), Weekly Production Summary (4), Estimated Finished Cost (5). Total Items: 34 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - SET DESIGN
    - Blue print of bridge and crew layout, art director Rolland Brooks, 5/13/66. 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - SHORE LEAVE (Prod# 17)
    - 1) First draft teleplay by Theodore Sturgeon, 10/3/66, w/annotations, 70 pgs. 2) Second draft teleplay, 9/9/66, 62 pgs. 3) Draft teleplay of Acts I & II, n.d., 39 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Sturgeon, Theodore (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 1) Original treatment by Theodore Sturgeon, 5/10/66, 14 pgs. 2) Revised treatment, 5/17/66, 18 pgs, 2 copies. 3) Rough step sheet/Structure, n.d., 7 pgs. 4) Revised rough step sheet, n.d., 4 pgs. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Script Materials: Revisions, loose pages (50), DeForest Research (2), Comments on teleplay (3). Total Items: 55 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Production materials: Credits (3, 3 copies), Shooting schedule (10), Cast list (3), Call sheets (7), Daily production reports (7). Total Items: 36 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 5/16/66 - 11/29/66. Total Items: 69. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Roddenberry, Gene * Justman, Robert * Sturgeon, Theodore * Hanson, Lee * Robertson, Stanley (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Financial Materials: Production budget report (4). Total Items: 4 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - SPACE SEED (Prod# 24)
    - 1) Story outline by Carey Wilber, 8/29/66, 18 pgs. (2 copies) 2) Story Outline, 9/1/66, 21 pgs. (4 copies) Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Wilber, Carey * Coon, Gene (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 1) First draft teleplay (Act I) by Carey Wilber and Gene Coon, 12/7/66, 17 pgs. 2) Teleplay by Carey Wilber, n.d., 66 pgs. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Script Materials: Notes on 1st draft teleplay (6, 2 copies), Notes by Harvey Lynn (19), DeForest Research (6), Revisions, loose pages (15). Total Items: 52 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Production Materials: Cast List (8), Call Sheets (2), Daily Production Reports (2). Total Items: 12 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, Writer's Guild of America, 9/2/66 - 1/23/67. Total Items: 54 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Daniels, Marc * Dorfman, Mary * Justman, Robert * Roddenberry, Gene * Coon, Gene * Robertson, Stanley (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Financial Materials: Production Budget Report (5), Daily Budget Reports (4). Total Items: 9 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - SPECTRE OF THE GUN (Prod# 56)
    - 1) Story Outline by Lee Cronin, 3/18/68, 13 pgs. 2) Story Outline, 4/19/68, 14 pgs. 3) Teleplay, 4/30/68, 56 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Cronin, Lee (pseudonym for Gene Coon) (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Script Materials: Story Notes by Arthur Singer (7), DeForest Research (8). Total Items: 15 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Production Materials: Credits Breakdown (8), Photographic Effects (2), Daily Production Reports (8). Total Items: 18 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 3/22/68 - 6/27/68. Total Items: 39 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Roddenberry, Gene * Freiberger, Fred * Justman, Robert (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Financial Materials: Budget Report (1), Budget Worksheets (24), Weekly Production Summary (24), Estimated Finished Cost (31). Total Items: 80 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - SPOCK'S BRAIN (Prod# 61)
    - 1) Story Outline by Lee Cronin, 4/22/68, 12 pgs. (2 copies) 2) Story Outline, 5/11/68, 10 pgs. 3) Teleplay, 4/16/68, 59 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Cronin, Lee (pseudonym for Gene Coon) (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Script Materials: DeForest Research (14). Total Items: 14 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 3/18/68 - 7/12/68. Total Items: 51 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Roddenberry, Gene * Messerschmidt, Jean * Dewey, Ray * Thompson, Foster D. * Freiberger, Fred * Justman, Robert * Robertson, Stanley (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Production Materials: Comments on Filmed Episode (1), Credits Breakdown (3), Photographic Effects (2), Daily Production Reports (6), Call Sheets (5). Total Items: 17 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Financial Materials: Budget Report (1), Budget Worksheets (24), Weekly Production Summary (19), Estimated Finish Cost (25). Total Items: 69 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - THE SQUIRE OF GOTHOS (Prod# 18)
    - Script Materials: Revisions, loose pages (49), Notes on 1st draft teleplay (3), DeForest Research (6). Total Items: 58 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Production Materials: Credits (3, 3 copies), Shooting schedule (7), Cast List (2), Call Sheets (7), Daily Production Reports (7). Total Items: 32 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: Desilu Productions, National Broadcasting Company, 8/15/66 - 12/1/66. Total Items: 20. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Schneider, Paul * Messerschmidt, Jean * Justman, Robert * Robertson, Stanley * Kerr, Walter * Roddenberry, Gene (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Financial Materials: Production Budget Report (6), Daily Budget Reports (5). Total Items: 11 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - A TASTE OF ARMAGEDDON (Prod# 23)
    - 1) Treatment by Robert Hamner, 9/12/66, 17 pgs. 2) Treatment, 9/23/66, 16 pgs., 3 copies 3) Story outline, 9/26/66, 17 pgs. 4) Story outline, 9/26/66, 16 pgs., 2 copies 5) Story outline, 9/28/66, 16 pgs. 2 copies Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Hamner, Robert * Coon, Gene (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 1) First draft teleplay by Robert Hamner, 10/17/66, 63 pgs. 2) Revised final draft teleplay by Robert Hamner & Gene Coon, 12/12/66, 60 pgs., 2 copies (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Script Materials: Notes on 1st draft (3, 2 copies), Notes on story outline (2, 2 copies), DeForest Research (6, 2 copies). Total Items: 22 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 9/15/66 - 12/23/66 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Justman, Robert * Robertson, Stanley * Coon, Gene * Roddenberry, Gene (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Financial Materials: Production Budget Report (5), Daily Budget Reports (5). Total Items: 10 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - THAT WHICH SURVIVES (Prod# 69)
    - 1) Story Outline by D.C. Fontana, 3/8/68, 14 pgs. 2) Story Outline, 8/8/68, 18 pgs. 3) Revised Story Outline, 4/12/68, 18 pgs. 4) Revised teleplay, 9/13/68, 62 pgs. 5) Final Draft teleplay, 9/16/68, 62 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Fontana, D.C. * Lucas, John Meredyth (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Script Materials: DeForest Research (12). Total items: 12 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 3/11/68 - 10/1/68. Total Items: 14 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Bays, Donald W. * Roddenberry, Gene * Justman, Robert (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Production Materials: Credits Breakdown (4), Shooting Schedule (8), Photographic Effects (5), Daily Production Reports (6), Call Sheets (6), Notes on Final Cut (1). Total items: 30 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Financial Materials: Budget Report (1), Budget Worksheets (24), Weekly Production Summary (8), Estimated Finish Cost (14). Total Items: 47 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - THIS SIDE OF PARADISE (Prod# 25)
    - 1) Treatment by Jerry Sohl, 6/15/66, 22 pgs., 2 copies 2) Treatment by Jerry Sohl, 7/?/66, 21 pgs., 2 copies 3) Treatment by Jerry Sohl, 8/9/66, 22 pgs. (2 copies, 1 w/annotations) 4) Treatment by D.C. Fontana, 11/15/66, 9 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Sohl, Jerry * Fontana, D.C. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Script Materials: Story Conference Notes (4), Notes on 1st draft teleplay (4), Notes on 2nd draft teleplay (2), DeForest Research (10), Comments from Gene Coon (2). Total Items: 22 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Production Materials: Credits Breakdown (3, 2 copies), Shooting Schedule (8). Total Items: 14 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 6/17/66 - 12/30/66. Total Items: 12 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Justman, Robert (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 1) First draft teleplay by D.C. Fontana, 12/7/66, 62 pgs. 2) 2nd draft teleplay by Jerry Sohl, 10/11/66, 64 pgs. (2 copies, 1 w/annotations). (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Financial Materials: Production Budget Reports (2), Daily Budget Reports (3). Total Items: 5 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - THE THOLIAN WEB (Prod# 64)
    - 1) Teleplay, 6/17/68, 51 pgs. (Incomplete) 2) Revised first draft teleplay by Judy Burns and Chet Richards, 6/25/68, 58 pgs. (Incomplete) 3) Revised teleplay, 7/11/68, 65 pgs. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Script Materials: DeForest Research (4). Total Items: 4 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 4/25/68 - 8/8/68. Total Items: 10 Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Messerschmidt, Jean * Justman, Robert (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Production Materials: Shooting schedule (5), Special Photographic Effects List (5), Call Sheets (6), Daily Production Reports (6), Credits Breakdown (5). Total Items: 27 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Financial Materials: Budget Report (1), Budget Worksheets (24), Weekly Production Summary (16), Estimated Finish Cost (22). Total Items: 63 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - TOMORROW IS YESTERDAY (Prod# 21)
    - 1) Story Outline by D.C. Fontana, 10/3/66, 16 pgs. 2) Story Outline, 10/3/66, 17 pgs. (2 copies, 1 w/annotations) 3) Teleplay, 10/31/66, w/annotations, 66 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Fontana, D.C. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Script Materials: Revisions, loose pages (21), DeForest Research (16). Total Items: 37 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Production Materials: Airing Sequence (3). Total Items: 3 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence/Inter-office memos: National Broadcasting Company, Desilu Productions, 10/5/66 - 12/14/66, 1/31/67, 2/28/68/. Total Items: 28. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Justman, Robert * Robertson, Stanley * Messerschmidt, Jean (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Financial Materials: Production Budget Reports (5), Daily Budget Reports (5). Total Items: 10 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - THE TROUBLE WITH TRIBBLES (Prod# 42)
    - 1) Story Outline by David Gerrold, 6/23/67, 23 pgs. 2) Story Outline, n.d., 35 pgs. Includes correspondence regarding or with: * Gerrold, David (Box 15, Folder 2)